<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adylan Roaffa</title>
    <link>https://adylanroaffa.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adylan Roaffa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 10:47:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adylanroaffa.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Failed Stoic</title>
      <link>https://adylanroaffa.netlify.app/posts/failed-stoic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 10:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adylanroaffa.netlify.app/posts/failed-stoic/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is me trying to be vulnerable. This post may offend or is too dramatic for some readers. So skip it if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to.
I am writing this post as a remembrance that I have failed to be a stoic. Sigh, I wrote this &amp;ldquo;stoic&amp;rdquo; thing everywhere in my bio. Turns out I don&amp;rsquo;t deserve one. At least for now.
The Incident Today, I have heard a lot of good news about my friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://adylanroaffa.netlify.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adylanroaffa.netlify.app/about/</guid>
      <description>Adylan Roaffa
Loves weird movies. Visit My Letterboxd Pretty good at FIFA. I hate the game, though. Gaming enthusiast. Compulsively buys a new video game every month. Rarely plays them. Currently working as a Software Engineer in Singapore. Passionate about distributed systems and system programming. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yet Another Blog</title>
      <link>https://adylanroaffa.netlify.app/posts/yet-another-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 14:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adylanroaffa.netlify.app/posts/yet-another-blog/</guid>
      <description>Just like every other developers in the planet, we tend to create a brand new blog every single year.
I try to keep it simple though this time. The goal of this blog is not to promote myself as someone that can build a website, but to learn how to write properly. I do not want it to be a &amp;ldquo;goal&amp;rdquo; like a year ago when I tried to create &amp;ldquo;30 Days of Writing&amp;rdquo; challenge and failed miserably in the middle of the challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
