<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adylan Roaffa</title>
    <link>https://adylanroaffa.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adylan Roaffa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:53:41 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adylanroaffa.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MM|25 - Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://adylanroaffa.com/blog/efficiency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:53:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adylanroaffa.com/blog/efficiency/</guid>
      <description>Efficiency is boring.
Modern world is all about the numbers. The bigger the better. The leaner the better. How to produce X by spending less than Y amount of money.
Imagine a world where everything is 100% efficient. Huge returns with near zero work. This world would mean nothing. Humans will only be consuming, not producing. Working is meaningless. Living is meaningless.
How do you optimize friendships? How do you optimize art?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MM|21 - Leadership</title>
      <link>https://adylanroaffa.com/blog/march-madness-march-21-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 22:11:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adylanroaffa.com/blog/march-madness-march-21-leadership/</guid>
      <description>Being a leader is not about giving the loudest roar to the pack. It is not about cracking the hardest whip to the slowest horse of the carriage. It is not about pushing and shoving.
A leader is all about example. A role model. Be the compass to the north star.
It is hard, yet fulfilling.
You need to embody the mission and share it with the rest. Guide, and empower your troops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Write</title>
      <link>https://adylanroaffa.com/blog/learning-to-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 21:09:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adylanroaffa.com/blog/learning-to-write/</guid>
      <description>Writing is thinking. To write well is to think clearly. That&amp;rsquo;s why it&amp;rsquo;s so hard. - David McCullough
I can now understand what differentiates between a good expert versus a great expert: the quality of their writing. Good expert understands how the thing works; great expert understand how the thing works and how to communicate it clearly. Clarity here is the keyword. If you cannot explain a problem clearly, you may not fully understand the problem yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Failed Stoic</title>
      <link>https://adylanroaffa.com/blog/failed-stoic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 10:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adylanroaffa.com/blog/failed-stoic/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is me trying to be vulnerable. This post may offend or is too dramatic for some readers. So skip it if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to.
I am writing this post as a remembrance that I have failed to be a stoic. Sigh, I wrote this &amp;ldquo;stoic&amp;rdquo; thing everywhere in my bio. Turns out I don&amp;rsquo;t deserve one. At least for now.
The Incident Today, I have heard a lot of good news about my friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://adylanroaffa.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adylanroaffa.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Adylan Roaffa
Loves weird movies. Visit My Letterboxd Pretty good at FIFA. I hate the game, though. Gaming enthusiast. Compulsively buys a new video game every month. Rarely plays them. Currently working as a Software Engineer in Singapore. Passionate about distributed systems and system programming. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yet Another Blog</title>
      <link>https://adylanroaffa.com/blog/yet-another-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 14:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adylanroaffa.com/blog/yet-another-blog/</guid>
      <description>Just like every other developers in the planet, we tend to create a brand new blog every single year.
I try to keep it simple though this time. The goal of this blog is not to promote myself as someone that can build a website, but to learn how to write properly. I do not want it to be a &amp;ldquo;goal&amp;rdquo; like a year ago when I tried to create &amp;ldquo;30 Days of Writing&amp;rdquo; challenge and failed miserably in the middle of the challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
